Alkesh Jadhav

Email: Alkesh.pro@gmail.com

Phone: +91-9404511510



Summary

An experienced Digital Marketing and Marketing Communication professional with a demonstrated history of working in the Information Technology industry. I love selling new work, challenging ideas and driving innovation within the organization. I have substantial understanding and experience with digital marketing tools and technologies like HubSpot, Salesforce Pardot, SEM Rush, MailChimp, HootSuite, Constant Contact, Google Analytics, StatCounter, Facebook Ads etc. I have a proven record of accomplishment in implementing online marketing strategies, from establishing digital presence of a new brand to outreach the presence of an existing brand. My professional skills includes Search Engine Optimization, Social Media Marketing, Email Marketing, Event Promotion, Marketing Research Initiatives, Content Creation and Promotion, Online Advertisements and much more.

Experience



Marketing Associate

Nov 2018 - Present

JLL India Property Consultants Pvt. Ltd. Aurangabad

ValuD Consulting has acquired by JLL since Oct 2018 for The transaction significantly enhances JLL's ability to bring the next generation of technology to its clients through future-focused innovation and deepened expertise in IBM's TRIRIGA*, Maximo** and Watson Internet of Things (IoT) services***



Marketing Analyst

Feb 2017 - Oct 2018

ValuD Consulting

ValuD is an acknowledged leader in providing business-facing technology solutions to Real Estate and Facilities Management organizations, with a focus on the implementation, training, and support of the IBM TRIRIGA Integrated Workplace Management System (IWMS). ValuD works with clients across a broad range of industries including Government, Media and Entertainment, Oil and Gas, Telecommunications, and Education, and throughout a broad range of projects—from targeted departmental solutions to global, enterprise-wide solutions with multiple users in multiple locations.

Primary Responsibilities:

- Marketing Communication
- Web Content & Design Creations for Event, Meetings, Campaigns & Roadshows.
- Marketing Automation with HubSpot and Salesforce Pardot
- Driving Outbound Email Marketing Activity
- Gathering and Analyzing Marketing Data,
- Managing and Driving Sales Productivity



Digital Marketing Executive

Jul 2016 - Jan 2017

WMS India Pvt Ltd, Pune

- Handling US, AUS, UK, Ireland, Germany and World Wide Based Projects.
- Google Analytics
- Google AdWords
- Google Keyword Planner
- Webmaster
- Site analysis
- Build keyword Strategy
- On-Page and Off page Activities
- Traffic Analysis
- Competitor Analysis,

Education



B.Tech Computer Science and Engineering

Maharashtra Institute of Technology, with First Class (7.3 /10)



Diploma in Information Technology

CSMSS College of Polytechnic, with First Class (62.94)

Skills



SEO • Research • Content Creation and Design • Social Media • Marketing Automation • CRM • Databases • Email Marketing • Analytics • Facebook Ads.

Certifications

- · HubSpot Inbound · Growing Business with Facebook ·Google Analytics · Email Marketing · Bing Ads Professional
- Google AdWords and Search Basics of Digital Marketing Qlick View- Beginner Infosys Campus Connect
- Certificate of Digital Marketing Learning Week from UpGrad

Personal Details:

Name: Alkesh Madan Jadhav

• D.O.B: 24-Feb-1993

Marital status: Single

 Address: B6- Shree Bhagirathi Residency Darga Road beside Jain International School, Aurangabad-431005